http://www.gbuwh.co.uk/page/privacy

View the UWH & The BOA page
Find a ClubHistory of UWH and the BOAWorld ChampionshipsOctopush NewsThe CommitteeBOA ObjectivesRules for Underwater Hockey (Octopush) General RulesSport DevelopmentUnder-19s Regional SessionsFree Trial of UWHSport Development FundClub ResourcesDocumentsDemonstration KitIntroductory Training CourseApplication FormSafeguarding and WelfareCOVID-19
Team GB
View the Team GB page
GB Mens SquadsGB Ladies SquadsHall of FameYouTube
Events
View the Events page
Competitions InfoNational Club ChampionshipsStudent NationalsNautilusLadies National Club ChampionshipsJunior National Club ChampionshipsCompetition Schedule and Past Results
Membership
View the Membership info page
Application For MembershipInsuranceCoaches and RefereesUWH Coaching schemeUWH RefereeingReferee CoursesQualified MembersProcedures for Club Membership SecretariesYour club membersRegister a New BOA ClubBOA Junior Section
Contact
View the Contact page
Leaflets, Posters & graphicsFAQsVoting
Visit our Shop
Menu
Events
Shop
Search
boa_svg_logo_with_puck
Join
Log In
Home
UWH & The BOA
View the UWH & The BOA page »
Find a ClubHistory of UWH and the BOAWorld ChampionshipsOctopush NewsThe CommitteeBOA ObjectivesRules for Underwater Hockey (Octopush) General RulesSport DevelopmentUnder-19s Regional SessionsFree Trial of UWHSport Development FundClub ResourcesDocumentsDemonstration KitIntroductory Training CourseApplication FormSafeguarding and WelfareCOVID-19
Team GB
View the Team GB page »
GB Mens SquadsGB Ladies SquadsHall of FameYouTube
Events
View the Events page »
Competitions InfoNational Club ChampionshipsStudent NationalsNautilusLadies National Club ChampionshipsJunior National Club ChampionshipsCompetition Schedule and Past Results
Membership
View the Membership page »
Application For MembershipInsuranceCoaches and RefereesUWH Coaching schemeUWH RefereeingReferee CoursesQualified MembersProcedures for Club Membership SecretariesYour club membersRegister a New BOA ClubBOA Junior Section
Contact
View the Contact page »
Leaflets, Posters & graphicsFAQsVoting
Visit our Shop
Home
About UWH/Octopush
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This website is operated by the British Octopush Association, an unincorporated association and the governing body of underwater hockey in the United Kingdom. The British Octopush Association (also referred to as 'the BOA' and 'we' in this policy) collects, uses and is responsible for certain personal information about you. When we do so we are regulated under the General Data Protection Regulation which applies across the European Union and in the United Kingdom. We are responsible as ‘controller’ of that personal information for the purposes of those laws.
This privacy policy relates to your use of our website. By using our website you agree to and are bound by our privacy policy.
What personal information do we collect?
Our community is largely managed online so our web application securely collects and stores the following information for registered members:
Personal details like your full name, contact information, address etc
Your date of birth and gender
Your account details such as username and login details
Your registered club
Logging information such as referee/coaching qualifications and experience
How is personal information collected?
Personal information may be collected when a registered user enters it into a form on the website. Some details that are provided to us externally may be manually input by us or on our behalf.
How is my information used?
Membership information is used for a number of reasons, all of which are specifically for the management and administration of the BOA and to provide services to you.
The personal information we collect may be used for the following administrative purposes:
To provide goods and services to you as a member, such as processing or renewing an application for membership with us, including the costs, the payment methods available and the conditions to attach
To provide electronic services that require us to establish a user’s authenticity
To manage competitions and events run by us.
We may use details to contact members directly to request further information needed to fulfil an original purpose. We may also use personal information to contact users by electronic or physical means including but not limited to:
Sending e-mail to those that have requested it
Contacting users to request additional information and clarification
Other electronic and physical correspondence.
Anonymous information that is gathered automatically without the explicit consent of the user (such as Google Analytics) will not be used by us to identify an individual.
We may use this information for the purposes of statistical reporting so that we are able to enhance the services we offer to our members and other users. We may make this information available to others to fulfil our statutory obligations.
What is the legal basis for processing your information?
Where we use your personal information we are required to have a legal basis for this. We rely on various legal bases to use your personal information:
Legitimate interests: where our use of your personal information is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of a third party (unless there is a good reason to protect your personal information which overrides our legitimate interests)
Legal obligation: where our use of your personal information is necessary for us to comply with the law (not including contractual obligations)
Consent: where you have given us clear consent for us to process your personal information for a specific purpose
Contract: where our use of your personal information is necessary for a contract we have with you (eg when you purchase items from the BOA shop), or because you have asked us to take specific steps before entering into a contract.
How long is personal information retained by us?
Unless we tell you otherwise, we’ll hold your personal information based on the following criteria:
For as long as we have reasonable needs, such as managing our relationship and service to you as a member
For as long as we provide services to you as a member
Retention periods in line with legal and regulatory requirements or guidance.
What should you do if your personal information changes?
If you have an account online with us there are some aspects of information - such as your contact details - that you can manage yourself via the edit profile facility on your account.
If your changed information falls outside of this, you should inform us - using the details in the Contact us section of our website - so that we can update our records. We’ll then update your records if we can.
Do you have to provide your personal information to us?
We do require your personal information for our BOA account. We would be unable to provide you with services as a member if you did not. Where providing some personal information is optional, we’ll make this as clear as possible.
What are your rights under data protection laws?
Here is an idea of the rights that all individuals have under data protection laws. The right to:
be informed about the processing of your personal information
have your personal information corrected if it is inaccurate and to have incomplete personal information completed
object to processing of your personal information
restrict processing of your personal information
have your personal information erased (the “right to be forgotten”)
request access to your personal information and to obtain information about how we process it
move, copy or transfer your personal information (“data portability”)
You have the right to put forward a complaint to the Information Commissioner’s Office which enforces data protection laws: https://ico.org.uk/. You can contact us using the details in the Contact us section of our website.
Security
We take reasonable precautions to ensure that the personal data gathered in the course of operating our website and administration processes is kept securely and within our control at all times.
Cookies
We use cookies to ensure that we can maintain a logged in state for your membership and also so that we provide the best website experience. If you continue to use our website for information or membership purposes, we will assume that you are happy to receive all cookies on our website.
Changes to this privacy policy
We may change this privacy policy at any given time by updating the content of this page to reflect any changes in the law and/or our own privacy practices. For this
reason, we suggest that you to check this privacy policy whenever you visit our website.
The current policy can also be obtained on request by contacting us using the details in the Contact us section of our website.
Contact us
If you have any questions or comments, or if you wish to exercise your privacy rights, you can contact us using the details in the Contact us section of our website.
Updated by Phil Thompson on 03/03/20
